const data = [
  {
    question: "What does UX stand for?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["User Interface", "User Engagement"],
    correctAnswer: "User Experience",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of wireframing in the design process?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "To add visual aesthetics to the design",
      "To create a high-fidelity prototype",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To outline the layout and structure of the design",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which color scheme is characterized by using only one color and its shades?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Analogous", "Complementary"],
    correctAnswer: "Monochromatic",
  },
  {
    question: "What does UI stand for?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["User Interaction", "User Involvement"],
    correctAnswer: "User Interface",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the primary goal of usability testing?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "To identify visual design flaws",
      "To evaluate the loading speed of the design",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To assess how easily users can complete tasks",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of a mood board in the design process?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["To organize user feedback", "To track design progress"],
    correctAnswer: "To showcase visual design options",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which design principle focuses on maintaining consistency in visual elements?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Hierarchy", "Proximity"],
    correctAnswer: "Unity",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the difference between UI and UX?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "UI is about the overall user experience, while UX is about visual elements.",
      "UI and UX are the same concepts.",
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "UI is about visual elements, while UX is about the overall user experience.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which file format is best for delivering high-quality graphics for web design?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["JPEG", "GIF"],
    correctAnswer: "PNG",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main objective of card sorting in UX design?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "To test different color schemes",
      "To gather user feedback on a design",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To organize content and improve information architecture",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In the design thinking process, which phase involves empathizing with the users?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Ideation", "Prototyping"],
    correctAnswer: "Empathize",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which type of user research involves observing users in their natural environment?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Surveys", "Focus groups"],
    correctAnswer: "Field studies",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of A/B testing in UX design?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "To gather qualitative user feedback",
      "To assess the loading speed of a design",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To compare two different design concepts",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which design principle focuses on creating clear visual paths for users?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Contrast", "Proximity"],
    correctAnswer: "Hierarchy",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main goal of conducting a heuristic evaluation?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "To gather user feedback on a design",
      "To evaluate the loading speed of a design",
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "To identify usability issues based on established principles",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which research method involves studying user behaviors and preferences through data analysis?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Qualitative research", "Ethnographic research"],
    correctAnswer: "Quantitative research",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which element of the design should be prioritized to improve accessibility for users with disabilities?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Color scheme", "Navigation structure"],
    correctAnswer: "Typography",
  },
  {
    question: "What does 'responsive design' mean?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Designing for different user personas",
      "Designing with empathy for users",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Designing for various screen sizes and devices",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Golden Ratio' in design?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "To define the brand color palette",
      "To establish a grid system for the design",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To create balanced and visually pleasing layouts",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which prototyping fidelity is characterized by a basic representation of the design without detailed visuals?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Medium-fidelity prototype", "High-fidelity prototype"],
    correctAnswer: "Low-fidelity prototype",
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to Apple's HIG, what is the recommended minimum touch target size for interactive elements on iOS devices?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["20x20 pixels", "40x40 pixels"],
    correctAnswer: "30x30 pixels",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which design principle from Apple's HIG emphasizes the importance of clear, consistent, and intuitive navigation?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Efficiency", "Clarity"],
    correctAnswer: "Navigation",
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to Apple's HIG, what is the recommended duration for displaying splash screens during app launch?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["2 seconds", "1 second"],
    correctAnswer: "3 seconds",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the recommended font size for body text in iOS app designs, as per Apple's HIG?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["12 points", "16 points"],
    correctAnswer: "14 points",
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to Apple's HIG, what is the primary focus for designing the layout of an iOS app?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Visual appeal", "Animation effects"],
    correctAnswer: "Usability and clarity",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In Apple's HIG, what term is used to describe the visual element that represents an app on the iOS home screen?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Logo", "Widget"],
    correctAnswer: "Icon",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which accessibility feature, as recommended by Apple's HIG, allows users to control their device using voice commands?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Switch Control", "Siri"],
    correctAnswer: "VoiceOver",
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to Apple's HIG, what is the suggested maximum length for a user-visible label on iOS?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["10 characters", "30 characters"],
    correctAnswer: "20 characters",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which design principle from Apple's HIG encourages designers to use a consistent grid system for alignment and layout?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Consistency", "Hierarchy"],
    correctAnswer: "Alignment",
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to Apple's HIG, what is the recommended minimum contrast ratio between text and its background for optimal legibility?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["3:1", "7:1"],
    correctAnswer: "4.5:1",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In Apple's HIG, what term is used to describe the visual effect that occurs when a user taps an interactive element?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Press effect", "Tap effect"],
    correctAnswer: "Touch effect",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which design element, as recommended by Apple's HIG, helps users understand their current location within an app's hierarchy?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Tab bar", "Navigation bar"],
    correctAnswer: "Status bar",
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to Apple's HIG, what is the recommended size for app icon assets for iOS devices with high-resolution displays?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["120x120 pixels", "60x60 pixels"],
    correctAnswer: "180x180 pixels",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which accessibility feature, as recommended by Apple's HIG, provides audible descriptions of on-screen elements to assist users with visual impairments?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Switch Control", "Guided Access"],
    correctAnswer: "VoiceOver",
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to Apple's HIG, what is the suggested maximum duration for microinteractions such as button animations?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["0.5 seconds", "1 second"],
    correctAnswer: "0.2 seconds",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which type of control, as per Apple's HIG, is used to gather textual input from users in a single line?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Text view", "Stepper"],
    correctAnswer: "Text field",
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to Apple's HIG, what is the recommended padding or spacing between interactive elements to avoid accidental taps?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["10 points", "15 points"],
    correctAnswer: "5 points",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In Apple's HIG, what term is used to describe the behavior where content bounces back when users reach the end of a scrollable area?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Elastic scrolling", "Snap scrolling"],
    correctAnswer: "Rubber banding",
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to Apple's HIG, what is the recommended duration for a standard app transition animation?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["0.2 seconds", "1 second"],
    correctAnswer: "0.5 seconds",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which accessibility feature, as recommended by Apple's HIG, enables users to control their device using physical switches or assistive devices?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["VoiceOver", "Siri"],
    correctAnswer: "Switch Control",
  },
];

export default data;
